cashu.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy describes the ways in which we collect, store, use and protect your personal information and it is important for you to review this privacy policy. By "personal information" we mean information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider anonymised information to constitute personal information as it cannot be used to identify a specific person.

By providing us with your personal information you expressly consent to us processing your personal information in accordance with the terms of our privacy policy.

We may amend our privacy policy at any time by posting a revised version on www.cashu.com. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it and, following such posting, your continued use of www.cashu.com, your CASHU customer account (Customer Account) and the related CASHU tools and services (collectively the "CASHU Service") shall constitute your express consent to us continuing to process your personal information in accordance with the terms of our revised privacy policy.

We last amended our privacy policy on 10th November, 2009 and we would encourage you to check www.cashu.com regularly for the most up-to-date version of our privacy policy. If we are going to use your personal information in any way other than the way set out in our privacy policy, we will notify you via email and you will have the choice of whether or not to allow us to use your personal information in such a way.

Our privacy policy will cover the following topics: our collection of your personal information our use of your personal information accessing, reviewing and amending your personal information our communications with you third party website links cookies competitions protecting your personal information how you can contact us about privacy questions

An order to open your Customer Account and start using the cashU Service, you will be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your date of birth, address, email address and telephone number and other identifying information which we may combine with your personal information. Additionally, in order for us to verify your identity we may need to request from you valid proof of identification (e.g. in the form of a copy of your passport, certificate of registration, your resident's visa/permit, your national ID card and/or your driver's licence).

You should ensure that the email address you have registered with us is always up-to-date so that we can always contact you with important information regarding your Customer Account and the cashU Service. We may also need to collect selected financial information from you, such as your credit card and/or bank account details.

Your Internet protocol (or IP) address (which is a unique number assigned to your computer server or your Internet service provider (or ISP), information about your computer (for example, browser type) and navigation information (for example, the pages you visit on www.cashU.com) along with the times you access www.cashU.com may also be tracked against your personal information for the purposes of preventing fraud, to improve the cashU service for you and, more generally, better manage our users' use of www.cashU.com.

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store the results when you respond to a survey.

We use your personal information to provide and improve the CASHU Service to you. We may also use your personal information to prevent illegal activities and implement our User Agreement with you.

For example, we may share some of the personal information you give us with banks (for example, to comply with our anti-money laundering obligations), to credit card authorisation, processing and verification services or for fraud screening purposes. We may need, in such circumstances, to request proof of identification from you (e.g. in the form of a copy of your passport or national ID).

These entities may not use your personal information for any other secondary purposes beyond the purpose for which your personal information was provided to them by us, unless they are required to do so by law.

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose your personal information to law enforcement agencies, government agencies or other third parties where we are compelled to by court order or similar legal procedure; where we are required so to do to comply with law; where we are cooperating with an ongoing law enforcement investigation; or where we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate a possible violation of our User Agreement.

In the event of a sale of CASHU Inc., its subsidiaries or affiliates or any assets of the CASHU business, your personal information may be disclosed to a potential purchaser for the purposes of the continued provision to you of the CASHU Service or otherwise in relation to the sale of CASHU Inc., its subsidiaries or affiliates or any assets of the CASHU business.

Otherwise, we will only disclose your personal information to a third party with your permission.

We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties in the normal course of doing business and will only share your personal information with third parties in accordance with this privacy policy.

You can access and review your information under "Profile" when you log into your Customer Account on www.cashu.com.

If your personal information changes in any way, if it is incorrectly presented in your Customer Account or if you wish to amend it for any other reason, you should promptly update, amend or correct your personal information (as applicable) via www.cashu.com.

Additionally, in order to deactivate your Customer Account you will need to contact our customer support team via www.cashu.com.

Following the deactivation of your Customer Account we may need to retain your personal information to comply with law, for technical troubleshooting requirements, to prevent fraud, assist in any legal investigations and take any other actions otherwise permitted by law.

Upon registering your Customer Account you will receive an email confirming your successful registration. Once registered, you may occasionally receive information on products, services and special deals from us.

We offer you the option of either receiving or not receiving such information when you register. Should you wish to change the option you chose on registration you can do so at any time in your Customer Account Profile.

www.cashu.com may contain links to other websites. CASHU has no control over the practices of these other websites and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites.

We encourage you, when you leave www.cashu.com, to read the privacy statements of each and every website you visit if you intend to provide personal information to such website.

Competitions may be made available on www.cashu.com from time to time.

You do not have to participate in these, however, if you choose to, you may be asked to disclose some personal information.

This privacy policy will apply to any personal information disclosed by you in relation to any such competition on www.cashu.com. At the time of entering the competition, it will be made clear to you who will have access to your personal information and the reasons for such access. You are, of course, not obliged to continue with your competition entry if you do not wish to disclose the requested personal information.

We hold your personal information on servers located in the United States.

If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and the storage of that personal information on our servers. We take reasonable measures to safeguard all your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure, including the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology with high security 128 bit encryption, certified by Thawte. However, the Internet is not a secure medium and we cannot guarantee the privacy of your personal information. You must enter your username and password each time you want to use the CASHU Service. Never share your username and password or any details about your Customer Account with anyone.

If you are concerned that your username, password or Customer Account has been compromised, please contact our customer support team immediately.

In particular, if you are concerned that your password has been compromised, please ensure you change your password immediately by logging onto www.cashu.com.

If you have questions or concerns about our collection and use of your personal information, please contact our customer support team at http://support.cashu.com/

**How do we use Cookie ?**  
When you access our website or use CashU Services, we (including companies we work with) may place small data files on your computer or device. These data files may be cookies, pixel tags, "Flash cookies," or other local storage provided by your browser or associated applications (collectively "Cookies"). We use these technologies to; recognize you as a customer or visitor to our website; customize CashU Services, content, and advertising to cater your needs; To measure promotional effectiveness; help ensure that your account security is not compromised; mitigate risk and preventing fraud; and to promote trust and safety across our sites and CashU Services.

We use both session and persistent cookies. Session cookies expire and no longer have any effect when you log out of your account or close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your browser until you erase them or they expire.

We encode our cookies so that we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our Cookies if your browser or browser add-on permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website and CashU Services. Refer to the help section of your browser, browser extensions, or installed applications for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling Cookies.

**Can I Delete Cookie ?**  
CashU cookies are in your best interest to promote trust and safety across our sites and CashU Services. If you still intend to disable our cookies please feel free to refer help section of your browser, browser extensions, or installed applications for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling Cookies.
